(Penny:)- Hey.
- Oh, how'd it go last night?
(Raj:)Oh, you know.
(Raj:)Same old, same old.
(Raj:)Looked through a telescope,
saw some stars.
(Raj:)Big whoop.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)You waited months
for time with that telescope.
(Leonard:)What happened?
(Raj:)Why? You writing a book?
(Sheldon:)I'm going to propose
a hypothesis.
(Leonard:)Last night,
Raj accidentally made contact
(Sheldon:)with an alien civilization
(Sheldon:)and has been ordered
by the United States government
(Sheldon:)to keep it a secret.
(Raj:)Nothing happened.
(Raj:)Can we please just
change the subject?
(Sheldon:)That sounds rehearsed.
(Sheldon:)We are not alone.
(Raj:)Hey.
Hello.
Hey.
(Leonard:)You get to play with
Raj's big telescope last night?
(Howard:)Whoa.
(Howard:)Where did that come from?
(Raj:)He never touched my telescope.
(Howard:)Way to go shutting up.
(Raj:)I did shut up. Now you shut up.
(Sheldon:)Fine.
Thank you.
(Wyatt:)I can't believe
you didn't call me this morning.